PRAYER TIME
Are you sick?
Are you on the sickbed?
Are you in bondage?
Are you in a cage?
Whatever situation you are in, this voice is not mine.
Demon, in highest places,
demon, in your home,
demon, in your career,
demon, in your life – you must obey!
I command you – leave my people!
Leave my people!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus!
I am a strong man.
Leave me alone!
Why are you disturbing me?
What have you done to his affection?
What is this?
I have destroyed it.
Leave me alone, I have to go!
He is so intelligent but he has to just do anything.
I block the way for his family.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Right now begin to confirm your release.
If you have confirmed your freedom let me hear your Amen.
[Amen!]
STANDARD FOR LIFE
People of God - Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
The person standing here in named Etumodor Jonathan. I am from Delta State, Nigeria.
I am here to thank God for delivering me from the spirit of man which had led me into male prostitution.
It all started at my tender age when I went to the river to swim.
In the river, I found myself defecating.
It never ended there.
During the night, in the dream, I saw myself swimming in the river.
I began to see myself having sex with and affection for my fellow men.
The spirit kept coming to me at night to have sex with me, even when people were there with me.
When the spirit came, I had to satisfy the spirit.
I had to go to the toilet to masturbate.
This continued for more than five years.
I had the affection for my fellow men.
This became a part of me.
This spirit had led me to travel to various states, having affection for my fellow men.
I began to do male prostitution.
Older men would meet me, have sex with me and pay me.
They used to book a hotel room to invite me.
For me to achieve the goal of the spirits,
I had to start using the internet.
One of the sites is Facebook.
Second is "To go".
Third "Badoo", and so many other sites.
I registered myself on this site, "Chat With Men", which I didn't know about.
They would have to invite me to their homes, even when their wife was there.
They had to put me in their guest room, telling the wife that I was someone from their office or friend.
At night, we did what we planned to do.
If they had not yet married, they would come to me and have what they wanted to have.
It would not be limited to married men.
It was for married men and people from my age group or below my age group.
This act continued.
I travelled to an extent that I had to initiate people into this evil act.
There was a time I realised some money from the prostitution I was into
which I invested and started a business.
Then, I was thinking of quitting this act but never did.
When I was not fully into it, I began connecting people.
People would call me to come to Abuja but I told them that I had some things to do.
I told them not to worry an I connected them to someone else.
I started connecting people when I was not there.
People would go and give me my commission.
The spirit of man affected my dressing and the way I behaved
which was far from what a normal man would do.
I saw myself as a woman.
If I talked, I would talk like a woman.
If I acted, I would act like a woman.
I dressed like a woman.
My hairstyle is just like that of a woman.
Everything about me was just like a woman.
The spirit encircled me in the form of a woman.
If I spoke, they would ask me, "Guy, why are you talking like this?"
This was what happened to me.
This spirit led me too far.
It had infected me with HIV/AIDS Positive – 1.
Even with this HIV/AIDS Positive – 1, the spirit never stopped there.
It started pushing me to do more.
I knew that I had this for six years but the spirit did not let me stop.
If it was for a normal man, he could have stopped.
To me, it started pushing me the more – I became more into it.
I began travelling more.
I started infecting people and the people I infected, began infecting others.
The people I initiated were infected and they kept infecting others.
This attitude continued.
It all happened that I opened up a business but the business was not doing well.
I had to stop and go back to full-time prostitution.
As I was doing the prostitution, I had a good job.
Prostitution did not allow me to do the job.
I lost the job.
Then, I went fully into prostitution.
I tried to stop.
I remember when I was in Enugu doing the business.
I went to some prayer houses where they prayed for me.
I thought it was over but it was not over.
I found myself still doing what I used to do.
I had to go back to Delta to still do the prostitution.
I went to some churches for prayer but it never stopped.
A spiritualist prayed for me, asked me to throw away my ring and assured me that it was all well.
I threw it away.
I went to Lagos but during my first week in Lagos, I did male prostitution again.
Someone paid me and I kept the person as a partner for me to sustain myself.
So, despite your efforts these spirits refused to leave and they continued to push you into male prostitution.
Had you ever experienced a kind of public humiliation because of what happened as a result of these spirits?
A lot
I experienced a lot.
When I was in Delta State, I was publicly harassed that I had to run for my safety and life.
If it was normal and there was no force in it, I would have stopped.
The spirit never stopped.
I had to run all the way from Delta to Lagos for my safety.
If I was a normal man, I could have stayed away from this that drove me from Delta to Lagos.
I still went into such an act; I never stopped.
OK. Tell us how did you come to be here at The SCOAN.
When I was in Enugu, I stayed with my sister.
Whenever I came to her house, she always watched Emmanuel TV.
If I came closer or touched the TV, I always found myself on the ground.
I decided that when I came to Lagos, I would come to The SCOAN.
When you finally came to The SCOAN and Prophet T.B. Joshua was ministering mass prayer; just tell us
what happened at that moment.
At that moment, I felt uncontrollable.
I was trying to hold myself from where I was but I was uncontrollable.
I remembered when the ushers were holding me and when I was on the ground.
That was how everything happened.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
That was how the power of God Almighty arrested our brother.
The evil spirit within him was exposed during the time of mass prayer, as we saw earlier in the clips;
how that spirit confessed what he had done to him and to his affection.
We can see it on the screen.
Tell us brother, to the glory of God Almighty; ever since your deliverance here at The SCOAN,
what has happened to you life.
Since my deliverance, I didn't see my fellow men the same way – I always ran away from them.
When I see a woman, I will know if she is smart, lovely.
I have begun to like women.
I don’t wear tight clothes or do any hair anymore; I begin to dress properly like a man.
I begin to see myself as a man.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
Right now, there is no more affection or attraction to your fellow men.
That spirit of man has completely left your body.
Yes.
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
We give all the glory to God Almighty for our brother's wonderful deliverance here at The SCOAN.
Looking back at you past; how did you feel thinking about how these spirits had pushed you to such
an extent of infecting so many men with the deadly disease, initiating men into this spirit?
Looking back; how do you feel upon, considering this?
I feel very sorry for what I have done.
To the people I had initiated, to homes I had broken
and to husbands whom I had taken away from their wives, I am very sorry for what I have done.
Please, it was not me.
We know it is not our brother, it were the spirits that actually pushed him to those acts.
It was beyond his own control.
We can just imagine how much havoc has been inflicted in the lives of many homes
as a result of this spirit and how many men have been infected with the deadly disease HIV/AIDS.
But we thank God that our brother is delivered and today he is set free.
In the light of this, what is your advice to our viewers all over the world?
Etumodor Jonathan Deliverance Testimony
We only have to hope on God for deliverance.
You may have it in mind that you were made that way but you are not made that way.
We are made according to the image of God.
Why do you want to go out away from God's image?
Please, wherever you are, run back to God.
It is only God that can deliver you from all situations.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
What our brother is saying here is that people having a similar problem, that are also affected by this spirit
of man or indeed a spirit of woman in the other case -
we know that deliverance from our Lord Jesus Christ is the answer.
That is why we are not here in any way to condemn.
We know that our Lord Jesus Christ hates sin but He loves sinners.
That is why we as Christians are to preach salvation and not condemnation.
That is why we thank God that the spirit that pushed our brother to such acts was exposed.
It is that evil spirit that we are fighting - not the persons themselves.
We thank God for our brother's deliverance.
We believe his testimony has really opened the eyes of many to realize this is a spiritual problem
and therefore requires divine intervention, and we believe that our brother is going to come back with more
wonderful testimonies to the glory of God, now that spirit has been kicked out of his life, in Jesus' name.
One more time; let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!